Yes, leave my goods.
You leave first.
I am not leaving you, you leave me.
Let's leave together on the count of three.  Ok
?
Yes, okay.
Three to one, I do
n't know from which garbage mom and dad picked you up.
So you are also not a fairy.  Get out
of here, monkey.
My
mom, I am going out.  If you have
any garbage to throw away,
give it to me.  Hey, it must be right in front of you, it must be on the
sofa.  See.
Leave it, friend.
This time I took it.  I didn't see it before,
you were looking at it today I want to see it, go and
see it too [laughs] it's done friend will I
get this of mine or take this, take it, let me
stay with you, I have had enough of
you friend if I tie a Rakhi
[music] then
now you will serve me, right, go and
see this only in your dreams, by the way
I do
n't want yours either, one of yours and one of mine,
mummy hey oh
hmm